(Sheldon:)Empty room.
If somebody says "Come in,"
I'm gonna freak out.
(Bernadette:)So, Emily, why did you decide
to specialize in dermatology?
(Emily:)I like cutting people with knives,
(Emily:)and all the other jobs where
you get to do that are illegal.
(Bernadette:)You're kidding, right?
(Raj:)She's scary,
but it's a cute scary.
(Howard:)Can I say just one more thing?
(Howard:)I had some kind
of food poisoning that day.
(Howard:)Sure, in retrospect,
gas station sushi...
(Howard:)Maybe not the best choice.
(Howard:)Nor was climbing out
your window and running away.
(Howard:)But I think we can all understand
how humiliating that was,
(Howard:)and I'd really appreciate it
if we could move on.
(Bernadette:)Howie, we moved on
a long time ago.
(Howard:)-I'm just saying--
-We moved on.
OK. Fine.